A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Photo Files, RG 1 FA1128
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller, Laurance S. and Family, 1880s - 2004; 9
  - Rockefeller, Mary French, 1910 - 1998; 3
    - Portraits (Champlain Studios), late 1920s-early 1930s; Grey or brown tone 6x9 prints, plus portfolio wrappers. (Box 47, Folder 705)
      Photos by Champlain Studios, NY. Two poses of MFR with short curled hair, collared shirt with simple pin closure.
    - Portraits (Delar), 1937-1938; OVERSIZED 7.5 x 9 black and white image on 11 x 16 mat, in portfolio cover. (Box O 97)
      Head shot of MFR, presumably taken from image of MFR holding Laura (see LSR Family, Portraits, box O 114).
    - Portraits (Eder), 1959; OVERSIZED Black and white 8x10 images on 11x15 mat board. Framed photo 12.5 x 15.75. (Box O 99)
      Portrait by Gabor Eder of MFR (5 poses, head and shoulders, wearing dark dress and pearls). 10 photos, plus one framed photo.
    - Portraits (Eder), 1959; Black and white 5x7 prints; 8x10 print proofs. (Box 47, Folder 706)
      Portrait by Gabor Eder of MFR (head and shoulders, wearing dark dress and pearls). Multiple copies, plus 3 proof poses.
    - Portraits (Erwitt), Undated; Black and white 8x10 prints. (Box 47, Folder 707)
      Two candid portraits of MFR seated in front of oil paintings. Occasion not identified. Photos by Boris Erwitt.
    - Portraits (Gallo), circa 1934; Sepia 5x7 image in 8x12 portfolio mat. (Box 47, Folder 708)
      Portrait of MFR by Michael Gallo, NY. Image fading. MFR in v-neck dress with pin, earrings.
    - Portraits (Henderson), circa 1949-1950; Black and white 8x10 prints. (Box 47, Folder 709)
      Lester Kierstead Henderson portrait of MFR in black dress with velvet cross-stripe detail and pearls. Two poses plus duplicates. Photo used for Society of MSKCC Salute to Summer Party, May 25, 1951. See also oversized prints, box O 98.
    - Portraits (Henderson), circa 1949-1950; OVERSIZED black and white 8x9 images on 11x13 mat. (Box O 98)
      Seated profile portrait of MFR in black dress with velvet cross-stripe detail and pearls. Two copies.
    - Portraits (Hill), late 1920s-early 1930s; Black and white 4.5 x 6.75 image in 8.25 x 12.25 portfolio mat. (Box 47, Folder 710)
      Ira L. Hill signed portrait of MFR in deep v-neck dress with necklace. See also oversized print, box O 97.
    - Portraits (Hill), late 1920s-early 1930s; OVERSIZED black and white 10.75 x 16 prints in portfolio cases. (Box O 97)
      Two undated portraits of MFR facing forward in deep v-neck dress with necklace and in profile.
    - Portraits (Karsh), 1979; Black and white, mainly 5x7 images on 8x10 paper; one 8x10 print. (Box 47, Folder 711)
      Yousef Karsh portrait of MFR on terrace at 834 Fifth Ave. Cropped image. Multiple copies, 2 poses.
    - Portraits (Karsh), 1979; Color 8x10 print mounted to approx. 8.5 x 11 mat. (Box 47, Folder 712)
      Signed Yousef Karsh portraits of MFR, both removed from frames: MFR on terrace at 834 Fifth Ave; interior shot of MFR in purple chiffon dress (had been in double portfolio frame with Karsh portrait of LSR).
    - Portraits (Karsh), 1979; Black and white and color 4x6-8x10, all on 8x10 paper or mats. (Box 47, Folder 713)
      Samples and proofs of Karsh portraits of MFR. Interior and exterior portrait shots. Includes one (self) portrait of Karsh on terrace at 834 Fifth Ave.
    - Portraits (Karsh), 1979; OVERSIZED Black and white and color, mainly 11x14 prints. (Box O 98)
      Proofs of Karsh portraits of MFR, and 3 finished photos. Interior and exterior portrait shots, with multiple poses and costume changes. 12 items.
    - Portraits (Koshiba), 1930s; OVERSIZED 12x16 black and white prints in portfolio covers. Includes one 8x12 print. (Box O 97)
      Three portrait images. 6 photos.
    - Portraits (Murray), circa 1952; OVERSIZED black and white 7.5 x 8.5 image on 11x14 mat, in portfolio covers. (Box O 98)
      Peter A. Juley and Sons photograph of Albert Murray portrait of MFR, leaning on fence at the JY Ranch. 4 copies.
    - Portraits (Rawlings), circa 1952; Black and white 7x9 print (removed from frame); 3 8x10 and 1 5x7 prints. (Box 47, Folder 714)
      Photo by Rawlings of MFR with arms crossed, wearing dark suit and striped scarf. Print removed from frame, plus duplicates. Press release December 1, 1952, announcing MFR's chairing of YWCA Centennial, attached to 5x7 print. See also oversized print, box O 98.
    - Portraits (Rawlings), circa 1952; OVERSIZED 11x14 black and white print on mat board. (Box O 98)
      Photo by Rawlings of MFR with arms crossed, wearing dark suit and striped scarf.
    - Portraits (Sherrill), 1934; Sepia and black and white 8x10 prints (multiple copies) (Box 47, Folder 715)
      Half-length portrait of MFR in light dress. Photo by Emery Sherrill Studios.
    - Portraits (Sippell), late 1920s-early 1930s; Grey or brown tone, 7.25 x 9 prints. (Box 47, Folder 716)
      Clara E. Sippell portrait of MFR in sleeveless dress with fabric (petal) detail on left shoulder. Two copies, both removed from frames.
    - Portraits (Wedding), 1934; Black and white 6x9-8x10 prints. (Box 47, Folder 717)
      Copies of two formal bridal portraits, full and half length. One photo used for press release for wedding, August 15, 1934.
    - Portraits (Wedding), 1934; OVERSIZED black and white prints in 14 x 19 portfolio mats (Box O 114)
      Two formal bridal portraits, full and half length, by Ira L. Hill, New York.
    - Blue Hill Troupe, 1940s-1950s; Black and white 5x7-8x10 prints. (Box 47, Folder 718)
      MFR in cast of unidentified Gilbert and Sullivan production. Photos nos. 5076-5081.
    - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1991 September; Color 4x6 prints. (Box 47, Folder 719)
      Two photos from A Christian Ministry in the National Parks dinner, September 12, 1991.
    - Foreign Policy Association Luncheon, 1979 December 18; Black and white 5x7 print. (Box 47, Folder 720)
      MFR with Margaret Thatcher and Walter Cronkite at Foreign Policy Association Luncheon, December 18, 1979, New York Hilton.
    - Friends, 1946, undated; Black and white and color, 4x5-5x7 prints. (Box 47, Folder 721)
      5 items: Carolyn Sheffield (photo and photo-postcard of her children at JY, 1946); Alice (Mrs. George) Bent (MFR's maid of honor) (3 pictures of her children).
    - Friends or Family (Unidentified), 1920s-early 1930s; Black and white or sepia prints, various sizes. (Box 47, Folder 722)
      Portraits or informal photos of various young women.
    - Friends (Unidentified), 1927; OVERSIZED black and white 10x13 print. (Box O 96)
      Formal portrait of unidentified young woman by the Cole Studio, Baltimore.
    - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary, 1980s-1990s; Black and white 5x7 and color 4x6-8x10 prints (Box 47, Folder 723)
      MFR with Garth Rosell and John and Aldryth Okenga; MFR on panel with unidentified man; MFR at podium and receiving award from President Robert E. Cooley. Photos of LSR and MFR with Billy Graham, at same event. MFR with LSR at board dinner, 1995.
    - Hudson, Dorothy H., Memorial Garden, Undated; 2 Color 8x10 photos; one 4x6 photo of plaque. (Box 48, Folder 724)
      Garden established at University of Texas, 1990; photo of MFR and (Dorothy Hudson), undated, ca. 1980? Includes letter from daughter Carline, (1990 or 1991).
    - Memorial, 1997 August 10; Twelve 4x6 color prints. (Box 48, Folder 725)
      Woodstock, Vermont. First Congregational Church. Dedication of a plaque in memory of Mary French Rockefeller. LSR spoke at ceremony; with Laura and Dick Chasin, and unidentified. Photos removed from album.
    - National Institute of Social Science, Undated; Black and white 8x10 print, in 9.5x11.5 mat. (Box 48, Folder 726)
      MFR with George H. W. Bush, (Fulton J. Sheen), and an unidentified man. Presentation of medal (either to MFR or the man). Photo by Wagner International Photos, Inc., NY. Photo removed from frame.
    - New York City Police Department Mounted Unit, 1980s; Color prints 8x10 and 5x7; 2 color negatives. (Box 48, Folder 727)
      MFR with detachment of NYC mounted police at Rockefeller Center; unidentified man also in picture.
    - Rockefeller for President Campaign, 1964; OVERSIZED black and white 11x14 photo. (Box O 96)
      Group photo of MFR, Elizabeth French Hitchcock, and other women, at a NAR for President campaign table. Sent by Arthur Daley, Rockefeller Campaign Headquarters. File includes note from Ruth Haupert to LSR.
    - Saint Peter's Church (New York), 1978; Black and white 5x7 print. (Box 48, Folder 728)
      Photo of MFR with Miss Lynch, Pastor Gensel, and Dr. Renwick, at Santa Lucia dinner, December 1978. Covering letter, February 8, 1979, acknowledging $5,000 contribution, included in file.
    - U.S.O. Luncheon, 1992; Black and white 8x10 print. (Box 48, Folder 729)
      MFR at U.S.O. Woman of the Year Luncheon honoring Barbara Bush, 1992. Photo with unidentified woman and her family (including a minister). Photo by D'Arlene Studios, Waldorf-Astoria, NY. See also photo in LSR and MFR file.
    - Whitney, Edgar, 1965; Color 5x7 prints. (Box 48, Folder 730)
      MFR painting instructor. Four photos of Whitney, dog, and painting setup. No photos of MFR. Includes copy of piece by Whitney on "Thoughtful vs. Thoughtless Watercolor Painting."
    - World Mercy Fund, Primum Vivere Award, 1981 September 25; Black and white 8x10 print (Box 48, Folder 731)
      MFR receiving framed award from Bishop Donal J. Murray of Nigeria and Father Thomas A. Rooney of Alexandria, VA, president of the World Mercy Fund. Dinner held at Waldorf Astoria Hotel. Photo by Sam Siegel, Metropolitan Photo Service.
    - YWCA, 1955-1959, undated; Black and white 8x10 prints. Several photos curling. (Box 48, Folder 732)
      MFR (as general chair of the centennial celebration) with John Foster Dulles and Mrs. Edward W. Macy, at YWCA Centennial celebration inaugural luncheon, January 11, 1955; MFR receiving tribute certificate from national board for her service as centennial chair, 1952-1959; unidentified group photo (world meeting, 1960s), removed from frame.
    - YWCA (Jacksonville, FL, Centennial), 1955; Album (9x11) with color and black and white prints; newspaper clippings. (Box 48, Folder 733)
      Presentation album and scrapbook on Jacksonville, FL, centennial celebration. MFR spoke at the banquet on March 4.
    - YWCA, 1959; OVERSIZED Panoramic Black and white glossy print, 8" x 20." In good condition. (Box O 138)
      World YWCA Meeting, Cuernavaca, Mexico, 1959. Panoramic group photo. MFR in back row. Image by Fot-Mex.
    - YWCA, circa 1962-1963; Black and white, 3.5x5 prints (Box 48, Folder 734)
      MFR trip to Fiji (and elsewhere) for YWCA.
    - YWCA, 1969, Undated; Color and black and white, 3.5x3.5 - 5x7 prints (Box 48, Folder 735)
      MFR at various YWCA events or trips
    - YWCA of the City of New York, 1969-1990; OVERSIZED Large leather bound album, of black and white 8x10 prints. Boxed. (Box O 115)
      Presentation album to MFR, documenting her service to the YWCA of the City of New York.
    - YWCA, 1970 May 20; Color 3.5x3.5 prints. Accordian pages in cube shaped album (4 x 4 x 1.5) (Box 48, Folder 736)
      World Service Council 50th Anniversary Celebration, Pocantico Hills. Photos in boxed accordian album.
    - YWCA, 1973, 1978; One 8x10 black and white print; 1 negative. (Box 48, Folder 737)
      MFR with Elizabeth French Hitchcock and two other women, 1973 (negative only; see print in Public Relations series, box 74, folder 1126); New York Times photo of Elizabeth French Hitchcock with two unidentified women, 1978, with covering YWCA letter to MFR, January 1979.
    - YWCA, 1992 April; Album (7.5x6.5) of 5x7 color prints (Box 49, Folder 738)
      MFR at YWCA World Service Council event honoring Elizabeth Luce Moore
    - YWCA, 1992 April; Two small albums of 3.5 x 5 prints. (Box 49, Folder 739)
      MFR at YWCA World Service Council event honoring Elizabeth Luce Moore. Duplicates of prints in other album.
    - YWCA, 1993 February; Color 4x6 prints. Pages removed from small, ring bound album. One 8x10 color photocopy of photo with identifying caption. (Box 49, Folder 740)
      LSR and MFR at YWCA reception for Queen Sophia of Romania and her daughters, at Cosmopolitan Club, New York.
    - YWCA, 1993 October 27; 4 black and white glossy prints (Box 49, Folder 741)
      MFR at YWCA Leadership Breakfast Gracie Mansion, NY; MFR and LSR at YWCA Women First Award Gala, NY, with Anne Stallard, National Board President and Dr. Johnetta Cole, president Spelman College. Nice images.
    - YWCA, Undated, early 1990s?; Small album of 4x6 color prints. (Box 49, Folder 742)
      MFR and LSR at Charlotte, NC, YWCA.
    - YWCA, 1994-1996; Color 4x6 prints (4 items) (Box 49, Folder 743)
      LSR and MFR at World YWCA 100th Anniversary, London; "Mary's Path," World YWCA Geneva, (1996).
    - YWCA, circa 1998; OVERSIZED Color 4x6 prints in slipcased 11x14 album. (Box O 100)
      World YWCA, Geneva, "A Vision for World YWCA Leaders, Mary's Walk" album. Walkway planted in honor memory of MFR.
  - LSR Family, 1937-2002; 4
    - Chasin, Laura: Portraits, 1954, Undated; Black and white 8x10 prints (2 shots, with multiple copies) (Box 49, Folder 744)
      Undated girlhood portrait; debutante portraits by Gabor Eder, 1954.
    - Chasin, Laura: Wedding, 1956; Black and white 4x6-8x10 prints. (Box 49, Folder 750)
      Wedding to James Herbert Case III, June 14, 1956. Formal bridal portrait by Gabor Eder (multiple copies); contact sheets with shots of Laura with LSR and with James Case.
    - Chasin, Laura: Wedding, 1956; Black and white 9x12 prints (Box 49, Folder 751)
      Wedding to James Herbert Case III, June 14, 1956. Formal bridal portrait by Gabor Eder, but not the same pose as in other file. Two copies, both removed from frame.
    - Chasin, Laura, and Family, 1964; 7 color slides removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 49, Folder 752)
      Images of Case family at Van Hornesville, NY. From LSR's collection of "Travel" slides, filed under "Van Hornesville."
      Material in the Rockefeller family collections that concerns the activities of living members of the Rockefeller family is restricted.
    - Chasin, Laura, and Family, 1970s-2000; Black and white and color 4x6-8x10 prints. (Box 49, Folder 753)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry), 1944-1980; Black and white and color 3x5 - 8x10 prints; 1 color negative (Box 49, Folder 754)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) and family, 1982-1994, undated; Black and white and color, 5x7 - 8.5 x 11.25 prints; 2 photocopies. (Box 50, Folder 755)
      Wedding, 1982; with LSR and MFR at formal event, June 1994 (NY Times photo); undated informal portrait, mounted on foamboard.
    - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) and family, 1980s; Color 5x7 prints mounted on foamboard. (Box 50, Folder 756)
    - Waletzky, Lucy: General and with Family, 1940s-1990s; Black and white and color 3 x 4.25 - 8x10 prints. (Box 50, Folder 757)
    - Waletzky, Lucy: Portraits, 1959; Black and white 8x10 prints. (Box 50, Folder 758)
      Debutante portrait by Bradford Bachrach, December 1959 (18 copies)
    - Waletzky, Lucy: Portraits, 1964; Black and white 8x10 prints. (Box 50, Folder 759)
    - Waletzky, Lucy: Friends and Family, 1962 May-June; 79 color slides removed from Carousel slide tray. (Box 50, Folder 760)
      School friends; Larry Rockefeller graduation, with LSR and MFR. Includes list of images.
    - Waletzky, Lucy: Russia Trip, 1962; 80 color slides removed from Carousel slide tray. (Box 50, Folder 761)
      Images from trip to Russia with unidentified friends or group.
    - Weber, Marion, 1951; Etching on copper, enclosed in 6.5 x 8.5 portfolio frame. (Box 50, Folder 762)
      Portrait etched in copper, sent as Christmas greeting from Marion to JDR Jr. and Martha Baird Rockefeller.
    - Weber, Marion, 1951-1956; Black and white prints, circa 4x6; 30 color slides. (Box 50, Folder 763)
      Portrait by Henderson, circa 1951; Marion on boat; high school graduation
    - Weber, Marion, 1956-1965; Black and white 8x10 prints. (Box 50, Folder 764)
      Debutante portrait by Gabor Eder, December 1956 (7 copies); with LSR at graduation from college, 1960; wedding portrait by Bradford Bachrach, 1965 (4 copies).
    - Weber, Marion, 1965; OVERSIZED Black and white 8x10 print in 10.5 x 13.5 mat frame and portfolio cover. (Box O 114)
      Wedding portrait by Bradford Bachrach.
    - Weber, Marion, and Family, 1974 - 1980s; Black and white 8x10 print and color 3x5 snapshots. (Box 50, Folder 765)
    - General, late 1940s - 1960s; Black and white 3 x 4" glossy prints. Color 3.5x4 prints. (Box 51, Folder 766)
      LSR and MFR, with two daughters and friends. Car packed for traveling; canal boat ride. Site unidentified; possibly at school or in England. LSR, MFR, by water, water-skiing.
    - General, Undated, circa 1950s; 117 Color slides, housed in mylar binder pages. (Box 51, Folder 767)
      Slide file of views, but including images of family and friends: Wyoming and Caribbean, girls' school groups, JY Ranch visits, horses, boats, Kykuit.
    - General, Undated, circa 1950s; 116 Color slides, housed in mylar binder pages. (Box 51, Folder 768)
      Slide file of views, but including images of family and friends: Wyoming and Caribbean, girls' school groups, JY Ranch visits, horses, boats, Kykuit, unidentified individuals.
    - General, Undated, circa 1950s; 1 color slide. (Box 51, Folder 768 A)
      Restricted - Open in 2029.
    - General, 1972-1974; 12 x 5.5 x 1 ringbound album; 3.5x3.5 color prints. (Box 51, Folder 769)
      LSR and MFR, with family and friends: at Woodstock, New York apartment, JY Ranch, Hawaii. Includes Ethan and Elizabeth Hitchcock; French family reunion; [LSR cutting down tree; board meeting at JY Ranch with LSR and Albrights, and Lady Bird Johnson.
    - General, 1988; Small album of 4x6 prints. (Box 51, Folder 770)
      LSR, MFR, with family, at breakfast table (Kent House?) and at Woodstock. Prints stamped 1988 July.
    - General (Negatives), Undated; Copy negatives (4x5), black and white and color. One package of unidentified color negatives. (Box 51, Folder 771)
      Assorted copy negatives of LSR, MFR, and family, plus a few relating to LSR business activities or unidentified. Includes individual and group family portraits, LSR and MFR wedding photo, LSR with Rickenbacker in front of Silver Fleet plane, LSR military portrait, etc.; 2 unidentified people on snowmobile, and in water. (From 834 Fifth Avenue.) One package of unidentified color negative strips also filed here.
    - Portraits (Delar), 1937-1938; OVERSIZED black and white 8x11 images on 12x17 mats, housed in portfolio cases. (Box O 114)
      Portrait of MFR holding baby (Laura) and of Laura sitting up in wicker bassinet.
    - Portraits (Towsley), circa 1940; Black and white 7 x 9 prints on 8.5 x 11 mats. 2 images. (Box 51, Folder 772)
      Portrait of MFR with daughters and Sentry, their dog; and of daughters alone.
    - Portraits (Towsley), circa 1941-1942; Black and white 5x7 prints on 9 x 10.25 mat boards (Box 51, Folder 773)
      Group portrait of LSR, MFR, and 3 girls, and of the 3 girls alone. Photos by Lena Towsley.
    - Portraits (Towsley), circa 1943-1944; Black and white 2.75 x 3.75 prints in 5 x 4.25 album. Photos glued to signed pages. (Box 51, Folder 774)
      Small album of portraits of MFR with the 3 girls. Photos by Lena Towsley.
    - Portraits (Henderson), circa 1945-1946; Black and white 4.5 x 6.5 prints, in 5x7 accordion fold album. Prints are loose or semi-attached in album. (Box 51, Folder 775)
      Small album with family and individual portraits. Photos by Lester Kierstead Henderson.
    - Portraits (Henderson), circa 1945-1946; Black and white, 4x5 proofs; some pages uncut (4 shots to page). Two black and white 8x10 prints and negatives. (Box 51, Folder 776)
      Unfinished proofs of photos taken in two sittings, but around the same date: MFR and 4 children, plus individual shots of the girls. MFR, LSR, and 4 children in library (photo no. 5064, plus negatives); some individual shots. Photos by Lester Kierstead Henderson.
    - Portraits (Henderson), circa 1945-1946; OVERSIZED BOX Black and white, 9.5 x 11.5 (print) and 11 x 14 (proof). (Box O 114)
      Finished portrait of LSR, MFR, and 4 children in library; finished portrait of daughter; unfinished proof of MFR and 4 children. Photos by Lester Kierstead Henderson.
    - Portraits, circa 1947-1948; Black and white 2.5 x 3.5 - 8x10 prints. (Box 52, Folder 777)
      MFR and girls in ruffled dresses (and wearing hibiscus flowers), and small snapshot of LSR with the 4 children on the same occasion, circa 1947-1948.
    - Portraits, circa 1947-1948; One 9.5 x 13.5 copy print. (Box O 114)
      MFR and children (same image as in folder 777.)
    - Portraits (Henderson), circa 1948-1949; Black and white 4.5 x 6.5 prints, in 5x7 accordion fold album. (Box 52, Folder 778)
      Small album with family portrait (LSR, MFR, and 4 children), and other groupings. Photos by Lester Kierstead Henderson.
    - Portraits (Henderson), circa 1948-1949; Black and white 4x5 proof prints. (Box 52, Folder 779)
      Unfinished proofs of portraits of LSR, MFR, and 4 children, plus other groupings. Photos by Lester Kierstead Henderson.
    - Portraits (Henderson), circa 1949-1950; Black and white 3x4 prints in accordian fold. Two images are creased and slightly damaged. (Box 52, Folder 780)
      Family portrait (LSR, MFR, 4 children) in living room, plus individual portraits of the 3 girls.
    - Portraits (Henderson), circa 1945-1950; 1965; OVERSIZED Black and white, 10 x 10.75, approx. 11 x 13, and 12.5x17. Spill (coffee?) on border of portrait of 3 girls. (Box O 114)
      Three separate finished family portraits of LSR, MFR, and 4 children, by Lester Kierstead Henderson, circa 1945-1946, 1948-1949, 1949-1950? Also includes finished portrait of daughter (1945-1946) and of 3 girls (1948-1949), as well as several unfinished proofs.
    - Portraits, 1956 December; Black and white 5x7-8x10 prints; 1 negative (Box 52, Folder 781)
      Family portraits (LSR, MFR, 4 children) taken at same time as Rockefeller Family Christmas portrait.
    - Portraits (Informal and Candid), 1940s - 1950s; Black and white 8x10 prints; 3 x 3 - 5x7 prints (black and white and color) (Box 52, Folder 782)
      Group photos of children with LSR or MFR. Includes enlargements of some photos in other files. Girls at beach with LSR; MFR and daughters with fish; at JY Ranch; Christmas at 834 Fifth Ave, children sitting on sled with dog; at Fishers Island with MFR and dogs; 4 children in riding clothes and on horseback, early 1950s (removed from frame); 4 children posed in the split of a birch tree, 1957. Group photo of LSR, MFR, and children, with others at unidentified event (standing before flags; may include Fairfield Osborn), mid-1950s.
    - Children, 1930s-1940s; Black and white, mainly 3.5x5; one 5x7 (Box 52, Folder 783)
      Baby pictures, MFR with infant, children at play, MFR on couch with daughters and stuffed animals. LSR with infant, and with 2 girls at Kent House.
    - Children, 1930s-1940s; Black and white approx. 3.5 x 5, matte finish. (Box 52, Folder 784)
      Baby photos; toddler girl playing; MFR holding baby girl; baby in crib. Some duplicates of photos in other files.
    - Children, 1940s; Black and white 3x5 glossy prints (Box 52, Folder 785)
      Early 1940s. Informal snapshots of children at play (cats; toy train ride; big dog). Some photos appear to be taken in Washington, DC: include photos of LSR in uniform with MFR, Ethan and Elizabeth Hitchcock, NAR, and children.